Finding Aid for Renewal Ministries videotapes, 1974-2009
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- The Choices We Face, VHS videotapes; beginning in 2002, the series included VHS and/or Betacam tapes
  - 2004, VHS tapes
    - Preserving in Dryness, 0408 (Box 18)
    - How Mary Changed My Life, 0409 (Box 18)
    - Youth and Families, 0410 (Box 18)
    - How to Share Your Faith, 0411 (Box 18)
    - When the Spirit Comes in Power, 0412 (Box 18)
    - Docility to the Holy Spirit, 0413 (Box 18)
    - My Marriage, My Conversion, 0414 (Box 18)
    - Drawn to Jesus, 0415 (Box 18)
    - Life is About Living, 0416 (Box 18)
    - God Alone, 0417 (Box 18)
    - The Lord is Our Strength, 0418 (Box 18)
    - Simplicity for Life for Lay People, 0419 (Box 18)
    - In Defense of Life, 0420 (Box 18)
    - Vocation, 0421 (Box 18)
    - We are Wonders in God's Creation, 0422 (Box 18)
    - Live Audience '04, 0423 (Box 18)
    - God's Hand in Our Marriage, 0424 (Box 19)
    - He's Calling My Name, 0425 (Box 19)
    - Jump Start Your Prayer Life!, 0426 (Box 19)
    - The New Evangelization, 0427 (Box 19)
    - Present Day Faith, 0428 (Box 19)
    - Hope in the Midst of Suffering, 0429 (Box 19)
  - 2005, VHS tapes
    - Therese, 0501 (Box 19)
    - Crisis and the Cross, 0502 (Box 19)
    - Missions, 0503 (Box 19)
    - Divine Mercy, 0504 (Box 19)
    - Humanae Vitae, 0505 (Box 19)
    - Life-Giving Love, 0506 (Box 19)
    - Companions of the Cross, 0507 (Box 19)
    - Discipleship, 0508 (Box 19)
    - Mary, My Mother, My All, 0509 (Box 19)
    - Six Keys of Spirituality, 0510 (Box 19)
    - Gift and Challenge of the Renewal, 0511 (Box 19)
    - The Sign of the Cross, 0512 (Box 19)
    - Eucharist, 0513 (Box 19)
    - The Law and The Lord, 0514 (Box 19)
    - Spirituality of Mother Teresa, 0515 (Box 19)
    - Spirituality Workout for Men, 0516 (Box 19)
    - Detachment, 0517 (Box 19)
    - Same-Sex Marriage, 0518 (Box 19)
    - In Him, We Overcome, 0519 (Box 19)
    - My Family, My Church, 0520 (Box 19)
    - Priorities, 0521 (Box 19)
    - The Reality of Evil, 0522 (Box 19)
    - Amazing Grace, 0523 (Box 19)
    - Raising Our Daughters, 0524 (Box 19)
    - Unbound, 0525 (Box 19)
    - Live Audience '05, 0526 (Box 19)
    - I Thirst, 0527 (Box 19)
    - Pocket Your Pride, 0528 (Box 19)
    - True Presence, 0529 (Box 19)
    - All For Him, 0530 (Box 19)
  - 2007, 0701-0730; BetacamSP (Box 21)
    (some program numbers missing)
  - 2007, 0701-0730; BetacamSP; closed captioned (Box 22)
  - 2008, 801-814 and 827-829; VHS tapes (Box 23)
  - 2008, 801-830; BetacamSP; closed captioned (Box 24)
  - 2009, 0901-0928; VHS tapes (Box 25)
    (include compact audio disc of selective messages)
- Other videotapes, VHS tapes
  - "Heart Basics" series, 12 videotapes (Box 26)
  - "Aiutiamo a cambiare coloro che amiamo" (Box 26)
    (program in Italian featuring Ralph Martin)
  - Medjugorje; Our Mother's Last Call with Sr. Emmanuel (Box 26)
  - Sr. Emmanuel of Medjugorje Mary's Messenger (Box 26)
- Publications
  - Books authored by Ralph Martin
    - The Catholic Church at the End of an Age (Box 27)
    - Husbands, Wives, Parents, Children, 2 copies (Box 27)
    - Hungry for God (Box 27)
    - Various titles (in multiple European languages) (Box 27)
  - Other books
    - A Cultural Approach for Christian Community by Richard R. Herman (Box 27)
    - On Evangelization in the Modern World by Evangelii Nuntiandi (Box 27)